Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Trust for New Music Records, 1996-2011
State University of New York at Buffalo, Music Library
- 1998, IV.; Item 1998-001-1998-071
  - Individual award recipients, 1998, A.; Item 1998-001-1998-005
    - Bitterman, Craig (Box 15, Item 1998-001)
    - Blum, Eberhard (Box 15, Item 1998-002)
    - Martinez, Patricia (Box 15, Item 1998-003)
    - Rutty, Alejandro (Box 15, Item 1998-004)
    - Seel, Daniel (Box 15, Item 1998-005)
  - Organization award recipients, 1998, B.; Item 1998-006-1998-013
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra [Dogs of Desire (Musical group)] (Box 15, Item 1998-006)
    - American Baroque (Musical Group) (Box 15, Item 1998-007)
    - Ensemble 21 (Box 15, Item 1998-008)
    - Ensemble Recherche (Box 15, Item 1998-009)
    - Escuela Universitaria de Musica (Box 15, Item 1998-010)
    - Pekarsky Percussion Ensemble (Box 15, Item 1998-011)
    - Percussive Arts Society (Box 15, Item 1998-012)
    - Society for New Music (Box 15, Item 1998-013)
  - Individual applications, 1998, C.; Item 1998-014-1998-021
    - Ascioti, Nicholas (Box 16, Item 1998-014)
    - Claren, Sebastian (Box 16, Item 1998-015)
    - Daniels, Mathew (Box 16, Item 1998-016)
    - DeWig, Karen (Box 16, Item 1998-017)
    - Dorvillier, Michelle (Box 16, Item 1998-018)
    - Fried, Joshua (Box 16, Item 1998-019)
    - Navok, Lior (Box 16, Item 1998-020)
    - Smeltzer, Jason (Box 16, Item 1998-021)
  - Organization applications, 1998, D.; Item 1998-022-1998-045
    - American Chamber Opera Company (Box 16, Item 1998-022)
    - Bronx Arts Ensemble (Box 16, Item 1998-023)
    - Consortium to Distribute Computer Music [CDCM] (Box 16, Item 1998-024)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 16, Item 1998-025)
    - Debussy Trio (Box 16, Item 1998-026)
    - Djerassi Foundation (Box 16, Item 1998-027)
    - House Foundation for the Arts/ Meredith Monk (Box 16, Item 1998-028)
    - Karaoke Awareness Project (Box 16, Item 1998-029)
    - Maelstrom Percussion Ensemble (Box 16, Item 1998-030)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Box 16, Item 1998-031)
    - Musica Nova (Box 16, Item 1998-032)
    - New Millennium Ensemble (Box 17, Item 1998-033)
    - New World Records (Box 17, Item 1998-034)
    - Other Minds Festival (Box 17, Item 1998-035)
    - Phantom Arts (Musical group) (Box 17, Item 1998-036)
    - Roulette (Organization) (Box 17, Item 1998-037)
    - Rova Saxophone Quartet (Box 17, Item 1998-038)
    - San Francisco Choral Artists (Box 17, Item 1998-039)
    - Sanford Dole Ensemble (Box 17, Item 1998-040)
    - Save the Music, Inc. (Box 17, Item 1998-041)
    - Schwungvoll (Box 17, Item 1998-042)
    - Warebrook Contemporary Music Festival (Box 17, Item 1998-043)
    - Washington Square Contemporary Music Society (Box 17, Item 1998-044)
    - Young Concert Artists (Box 17, Item 1998-045)
  - Audio recordings, 1998, E.; Item 1998-046-1998-071
    - Ascioti, Nicholas (Box 18, Item 1998-046)
    - Bitterman, Craig (Box 18, Item 1998-047)
    - Daniels, Mathew (Box 18, Item 1998-048)
    - Martinez, Patricia (Box 18, Item 1998-049)
    - Navok, Lior (Box 18, Item 1998-050)
    - Rutty, Alejandro (Box 18, Item 1998-051)
    - Seel, Daniel (Box 18, Item 1998-052)
    - Smeltzer, Jason (Box 18, Item 1998-053)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra [Dogs of Desire (Musical group)] (Box 18, Item 1998-054)
    - American Baroque (Musical group) (Box 18, Item 1998-055)
    - American Chamber Opera Company (Box 18, Item 1998-056)
    - Bronx Arts Ensemble (Box 18, Item 1998-057)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 18, Item 1998-058)
    - Debussy Trio (Box 18, Item 1998-059)
    - Debussy Trio (Box 18, Item 1998-060)
    - Ensemble 21 (Box 18, Item 1998-061)
    - Ensemble Recherche (Box 19, Item 1998-062)
    - Escuela Universitaria de Musica (Box 19, Item 1998-063)
    - Hiller Computer Music Studios (Box 19, Item 1998-064)
    - Maelstrom Percussion Ensemble (Box 19, Item 1998-065)
    - Phantom Arts (Musical group) (Box 19, Item 1998-066)
    - Sanford Dole Ensemble (Box 19, Item 1998-067)
    - Save the Music, Inc. (Box 19, Item 1998-068)
    - Schwungvoll (Box 19, Item 1998-069)
    - Society for New Music (Box 19, Item 1998-070)
    - Warsaw Percussion Group (Box 19, Item 1998-071)
- 1999, V.; Item 1999-001-1999-126
  - Individual award recipients, 1999, A.; Item 1999-001-1999-004
    - Bloch-Bonhoff, Thomas (Box 20, Item 1999-001)
    - DeWig, Karen (Box 20, Item 1999-002)
    - Mints, Arina (Box 20, Item 1999-003)
    - Okoye, Nkeiru (Box 20, Item 1999-004)
  - Organization award recipients, 1999, B.; Item 1999-005-1999-012
    - Barton Workshop (Box 20, Item 1999-005)
    - Bennington College (Box 20, Item 1999-006)
    - Boston Modern Orchestra Project (Box 20, Item 1999-007)
    - Electronic Music Foundation (Box 20, Item 1999-008)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 20, Item 1999-009)
    - newEar (Musical group) (Box 20, Item 1999-010)
    - New Millennium Ensemble (Box 20, Item 1999-011)
    - Roulette (Organization) (Box 20, Item 1999-012)
  - Individual applications, 1999, C.; Item 1999-013-1999-034
    - Anthin, Christopher (Box 21, Item 1999-013)
    - Battey, Bret, 1967- (Box 21, Item 1999-014)
    - Bowers, Greg (Box 21, Item 1999-015)
    - Burtner, Matthew, 1970- (Box 21, Item 1999-016)
    - Doynikov, Andrey (Box 21, Item 1999-017)
    - Erickson, Kurt (Box 21, Item 1999-018)
    - Garrop, Stacy, 1969- (Box 21, Item 1999-019)
    - Hammons, Lee (Box 21, Item 1999-020)
    - Heila, Daniel (Box 21, Item 1999-021)
    - Heller, Brian (Box 21, Item 1999-022)
    - Johnson, Aaron, 1970- (Box 21, Item 1999-023)
    - Kaefer, John F. (Box 21, Item 1999-024)
    - Kedem, Benjamin (Box 21, Item 1999-025)
    - LaCroix, Michael (Box 21, Item 1999-026)
    - Manthey, Robert M. (Box 21, Item 1999-027)
    - May, Andrew (Box 21, Item 1999-028)
    - McMullin, David (Box 21, Item 1999-029)
    - Penman, Joshua, 1979- (Box 21, Item 1999-030)
    - Tavadze, Jemal (Box 21, Item 1999-031)
    - Thomas, Kelland (Box 21, Item 1999-032)
    - Trout, Gilbert (Box 21, Item 1999-033)
    - Yanes, Adalberto (Box 21, Item 1999-034)
  - Organization applications, 1999, D.; Item 1999-035-1999-076
    - American Chamber Opera Company (Box 22, Item 1999-035)
    - American Composers Forum (Box 22, Item 1999-036)
    - Astral Artistic Services (Box 22, Item 1999-037)
    - Cabrillo Music Festival (Box 22, Item 1999-038)
    - Cantori di New York (Box 22, Item 1999-039)
    - Capital Composers Alliance (Box 22, Item 1999-040)
    - Chanticleer (Musical Group) (Box 22, Item 1999-041)
    - Common Sense Composers Collective (Box 22, Item 1999-042)
    - CORE Ensemble (Box 22, Item 1999-043)
    - CUBE (Box 22, Item 1999-044)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 22, Item 1999-045)
    - Debussy Trio (Box 22, Item 1999-046)
    - Dinosaur Annex Music Ensemble (Box 22, Item 1999-047)
    - DUO-96 (Box 22, Item 1999-048)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 23, Item 1999-049)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 23, Item 1999-050)
    - Extension Works (Musical group) (Box 23, Item 1999-051)
    - Florida International University (Box 23, Item 1999-052)
    - Formosa Chamber Music Society, Inc. (Box 23, Item 1999-053)
    - Kaufmann Center / Merkin Hall (Box 23, Item 1999-054)
    - Left Coast Chamber Ensemble (Box 23, Item 1999-055)
    - Longy School of Music (Box 23, Item 1999-056)
    - Meridian Gallery (Box 23, Item 1999-057)
    - Moebius Ensemble (Box 23, Item 1999-058)
    - Music Factory (Musical group) (Box 23, Item 1999-059)
    - New World Records (Box 23, Item 1999-060)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 23, Item 1999-061)
    - North/South Consonance (Musical group) (Box 24, Item 1999-062)
    - Old First Concerts (Box 24, Item 1999-063)
    - Other Minds Ensemble (Box 24, Item 1999-064)
    - Paul Dresher Ensemble (Box 24, Item 1999-065)
    - Providence Productions (Box 24, Item 1999-066)
    - Relâche - The Ensemble for Contemporary Music (Box 24, Item 1999-067)
    - ROVA Saxophone Quartet (Box 24, Item 1999-068)
    - Seal Bay Festival of American Chamber Music (Box 24, Item 1999-069)
    - Solaris (Musical group) (Box 24, Item 1999-070)
    - St. Ignatius of Antioch Episcopal Church (New York, N.Y.) (Box 24, Item 1999-071)
    - Studio of Electronic Music, Inc. (Box 24, Item 1999-072)
    - Top Brass (Box 24, Item 1999-073)
    - V International Guitar Congress-Festival (Box 24, Item 1999-074)
    - Vienna Modern Masters (Box 24, Item 1999-075)
    - Warebrook Contemporary Music Festival (Box 24, Item 1999-076)
  - Audio recordings, 1999, E.; Item 1999-077-1999-126
    - Anthin, Christopher (Box 25, Item 1999-077)
    - Battey, Bret (Box 25, Item 1999-078)
    - Battey, Bret (Box 25, Item 1999-079)
    - Bloch-Bonhoff, Thomas (Box 25, Item 1999-080)
    - Bowers, Greg (Box 25, Item 1999-081)
    - DeWig, Karen (Box 25, Item 1999-082)
    - Erickson, Kurt (Box 25, Item 1999-083)
    - Garrop, Stacy, 1969- (Box 25, Item 1999-084)
    - Hammons, Lee (Box 25, Item 1999-085)
    - Heila, Daniel (Box 25, Item 1999-086)
    - Heller, Brian (Box 25, Item 1999-087)
    - Johnson, Aaron, 1970- (Box 25, Item 1999-088)
    - Kaefer, John (Box 25, Item 1999-089)
    - Kedem, Benjamin (Box 25, Item 1999-090)
    - Manthey, Robert (Box 25, Item 1999-091)
    - May, Andrew (Box 25, Item 1999-092)
    - Okoye, Nkeiru (Box 25, Item 1999-093)
    - Penman, Joshua, 1979- (Box 25, Item 1999-094)
    - Tavadze, Jemal (Box 25, Item 1999-095)
    - Thomas, Kelland (Box 25, Item 1999-096)
    - Trout, Gilbert (Box 25, Item 1999-097)
    - Yanes, Adalberto (Box 26, Item 1999-098)
    - American Composers Forum (Box 26, Item 1999-099)
    - Barton Workshop (Box 26, Item 1999-100)
    - Boston Modern Orchestra Project (Box 26, Item 1999-101)
    - Cabrillo Music Festival (Box 26, Item 1999-102)
    - Cantori di New York (Box 26, Item 1999-103)
    - Chanticleer (Musical group) (Box 26, Item 1999-104)
    - Common Sense Composers Collective (Box 26, Item 1999-105)
    - CORE Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-106)
    - Cygnus Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-107)
    - Debussy Trio (Box 26, Item 1999-108)
    - Dinosaur Annex Music Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-109)
    - DUO-96 (Box 26, Item 1999-110)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 26, Item 1999-111)
    - Extension Works (Musical group) (Box 26, Item 1999-112)
    - Left Coast Chamber Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-113)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 26, Item 1999-114)
    - Locrian Chamber Players (Box 26, Item 1999-115)
    - Moebius Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-116)
    - newEar (Musical group) (Box 26, Item 1999-117)
    - New Millennium Ensemble (Box 26, Item 1999-118)
    - New Millennium Ensemble (Box 27, Item 1999-119)
    - New York Treble Singers (Box 27, Item 1999-120)
    - Paul Dresher Ensemble (Box 27, Item 1999-121)
    - Relache: The Ensemble for Contemporary Music (Box 27, Item 1999-122)
    - ROVA Saxophone Quartet (Box 27, Item 1999-123)
    - Seal Bay Festival of American Chamber Music (Box 27, Item 1999-124)
    - St. Ignatius of Antioch Episcopal Church (New York, N.Y.) (Box 27, Item 1999-125)
    - Top Brass (Box 27, Item 1999-126)
- 2000, VI.; Item 2000-001-2000-086
  Arranged into six subseries:
  F. Scores
  - Individual award recipients, 2000, A.; Item 2000-001-2000-007
    - Chase, Claire (Box 28, Item 2000-001)
    - German, Lyudmila (Box 28, Item 2000-002)
    - Jessen, Edward (Box 28, Item 2000-003)
    - Nonken, Marilyn (Box 28, Item 2000-004)
    - Osado, Moto (Box 28, Item 2000-005)
    - Samuelson, Eric (Box 28, Item 2000-007)
    - Swist, Christopher (Box 28, Item 2000-007)
  - Organization award recipients, 2000, B.; Item 2000-008-2000-013
    - Aldeburgh Productions (Box 29, Item 2000-008)
    - Almeida Theatre (Box 29, Item 2000-009)
    - Carre Recorder Quartet (Box 29, Item 2000-010)
    - June in Buffalo (Box 29, Item 2000-011)
    - Manhattan Virtuosi (Box 29, Item 2000-012)
    - Minimum Security Composers Collective (Box 29, Item 2000-0013)
  - Individual applications, 2000, C.; Item 2000-014-2000-023
    - Doynikov, Andrey (Box 30, Item 2000-014)
    - Flenaugh, Tanitra (Box 30, Item 2000-015)
    - Gordon, Geoffrey (Box 30, Item 2000-016)
    - Guberman, Morgan (Box 30, Item 2000-017)
    - Hallman, Joseph (Box 30, Item 2000-018)
    - Heila, Daniel (Box 30, Item 2000-019)
    - Johnson, Jessica (Box 30, Item 2000-020)
    - Lauten, Elodie (Box 30, Item 2000-021)
    - McMullin, David (Box 30, Item 2000-022)
    - Zhazylbekova, Zhamilya (Box 30, Item 2000-023)
  - Organization applications, 2000, D.; Item 2000-024-2000-049
    - Artona (Musical group) (Box 31, Item 2000-024)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 31, Item 2000-025)
    - Cabrillo Music Festival (Box 31, Item 2000-026)
    - Colorado Music Festival (Box 31, Item 2000-027)
    - Common Sense Composers Collective (Box 31, Item 2000-028)
    - The Core Ensemble (Box 31, Item 2000-029)
    - CUBE Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 31, Item 2000-030)
    - Da Capo Chamber Players (Box 31, Item 2000-031)
    - Das Neue Ensemble (Box 32, Item 2000-032)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 32, Item 2000-033)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 32, Item 2000-034)
    - Houston Composers Alliance (Box 32, Item 2000-035)
    - Living Artist Recordings (Box 32, Item 2000-036)
    - Meridian Gallery (Box 32, Item 2000-037)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Box 32, Item 2000-038)
    - Metamorphosen Chamber Orchestra (Box 32, Item 2000-039)
    - New England Philharmonic (Box 32, Item 2000-040)
    - New York Treble Singers (Musical group) (Box 32, Item 2000-041)
    - North/South Consonance (Musical group) (Box 32, Item 2000-042)
    - Other Minds Festival (Box 33, Item 2000-043)
    - Rova Saxophone Quartet (Box 33, Item 2000-044)
    - San Francisco Contemporary Music Players (Box 33, Item 2000-045)
    - The Walden School (Box 33, Item 2000-046)
    - Warebrook Contemporary Music Festival (Box 33, Item 2000-047)
    - Young Concert Artists (Box 33, Item 2000-048)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 33, Item 2000-049)
  - Audio recordings, 2000, E.; Item 2000-050-2000-084
    - Doynikov, Andrey (Box 34, Item 2000-050)
    - German, Lyudmila (Box 34, Item 2000-051)
    - Gordon, Geoffrey (Box 34, Item 2000-052)
    - Gordon, Geoffrey (Box 34, Item 2000-053)
    - Guberman, Morgan (Box 34, Item 2000-054)
    - Hallman, Joseph (Box 34, Item 2000-055)
    - Heila, Daniel (Box 34, Item 2000-056)
    - Jessen, Edward (Box 34, Item 2000-057)
    - Jessen, Edward (Box 34, Item 2000-058)
    - Nonken, Marilyn (Box 34, Item 2000-059)
    - Osada, Moto (Box 34, Item 2000-060)
    - Samuelson, Eric (Box 34, Item 2000-061)
    - Swist, Christopher (Box 34, Item 2000-062)
    - Zhazylbekova, Zhamilya (Box 34, Item 2000-063)
    - Flenaugh, Tanitra (Box 34, Item 2000-064)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 35, Item 2000-065)
    - Cabrillo Music Festival (Box 35, Item 2000-066)
    - Carre Recorder Quartet (Box 35, Item 2000-067)
    - Colorado Music Festival (Box 35, Item 2000-068)
    - The Core Ensemble (Box 35, Item 2000-069)
    - Da Capo Chamber Players (Box 35, Item 2000-070)
    - Da Capo Chamber Players (Box 35, Item 2000-071)
    - Das Neue Ensemble (Box 35, Item 2000-072)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 35, Item 2000-073)
    - Elan Trio (Box 35, Item 2000-074)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 35, Item 2000-075)
    - Living Artist Recordings (Box 35, Item 2000-076)
    - Manhattan Virtuosi (Box 35, Item 2000-077)
    - Metamorphosen Chamber Orchstra (Box 35, Item 2000-078)
    - New York Treble Singers (Musical group) (Box 35, Item 2000-079)
    - North/South Consonance (Musical group) (Box 35, Item 2000-080)
    - Rova Saxophone Quartet (Box 35, Item 2000-081)
    - San Francisco Contemporary Music Players (Box 35, Item 2000-082)
    - Non Sequitur (Box 35, Item 2000-083)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 35, Item 2000-084)
  - Scores, 2000, F.; Item 2000-085-2000-086
    - Hallman, Joseph Danza, 1999, 11 p. of music; 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2000-085)
      For solo harp.
    - Hallman, Joseph Sonata, 1999, 1 score (18 p.); 28 cm. (Box 80, Item 2000-086)
      For violin and piano.
- 2001, VII.; Item 2001-001-2001-098
  A.Individual award recipients
  - Individual award recipients, 2001, A.; Item 2001-001-2001-005
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 36, Item 2001-001)
    - Klopotic, Julianne (Box 36, Item 2001-002)
    - Mirelman, Sam (Box 36, Item 2001-003)
    - O'Donnell, Heather (Box 36, Item 2001-004)
    - Silverman, Adam (Box 36, Item 2001-005)
  - Organization award recipients, 2001, B.; Item 2001-006-2001-013
    - Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Box 36, Item 2001-006)
    - Catskill Conservatory (Box 36, Item 2001-007)
    - Hallwalls Contemporary Arts Center (Box 36, Item 2001-008)
    - New Music Works (Box 36, Item 2001-009)
    - New York New Music Ensemble (Box 36, Item 2001-010)
    - Parnassus (Box 36, Item 2001-011)
    - Riverside Symphony (Box 36, Item 2001-012)
    - Tzadik Records/Hips Road (Box 36, Item 2001-013)
  - Individual applications, 2001, C.; Item 2001-014-2001-028
    - Beakes, Jennifer (Box 37, Item 2001-014)
    - Bugallo, Helena (Box 37, Item 2001-015)
    - Currie, Elizabeth (Box 37, Item 2001-016)
    - Davenport, Kimberly (Box 37, Item 2001-017)
    - Fung, Vivian (Box 37, Item 2001-018)
    - Infanti, Andrew (Box 37, Item 2001-019)
    - Lavandera, Pablo (Box 37, Item 2001-020)
    - MacDonald, Peyton (Box 37, Item 2001-021)
    - Nicely, Tiffany (Box 37, Item 2001-022)
    - Reinhardt, Haleigh (Box 37, Item 2001-023)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas (Box 37, Item 2001-024)
    - Smith, Steven Lyle (Box 37, Item 2001-025)
    - Van Nostrand, Jill (Box 37, Item 2001-026)
    - Wramage, Greg (Box 37, Item 2001-027)
    - Zamboni, Mauricio Gomes (Box 37, Item 2001-028)
  - Organization applications, 2001, D.; Item 2001-029-2001-058
    - 3rd Angle (Box 37, Item 2001-029)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 37, Item 2001-030)
    - American Baroque (Box 37, Item 2001-031)
    - Armenian Contemporary Music Center (Box 37, Item 2001-032)
    - Astral Artistic Services (Box 37, Item 2001-0033)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 38, Item 2001-034)
    - Bang on a Can (Box 38, Item 2001-035)
    - Chicago Cultural Center Foundation (Box 38, Item 2001-036)
    - CNMAT (Box 38, Item 2001-037)
    - Colorado Music Festival (Box 38, Item 2001-038)
    - The Core Ensemble (Box 38, Item 2001-039)
    - CUBE Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 38, Item 2001-040)
    - Das Neue Ensemble (Box 38, Item 2001-041)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 38, Item 2001-042)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 38, Item 2001-043)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 38, Item 2001-044)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Box 39, Item 2001-045)
    - North/South Consonance (Box 39, Item 2001-046)
    - Orchestra 2001 (Box 39, Item 2001-047)
    - Other Minds (Box 39, Item 2001-048)
    - Pauline Oliveros Foundations (Box 39, Item 2001-049)
    - Pekarsky Percussion Ensemble (Box 39, Item 2001-050)
    - Savannah Symphony Orchestra (Box 39, Item 2001-051)
    - Society for New Music (Box 39, Item 2001-052)
    - Tacoma New Music (Box 39, Item 2001-053)
    - Voices of Change (Box 39, Item 2001-054)
    - The Walden School (Box 39, Item 2001-055)
    - Warebook Contemporary Music Festival (Box 39, Item 2001-056)
    - Young Concert Artists (Box 39, Item 2001-057)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 39, Item 2001-058)
  - Audio recordings, 2001, E.; Item 2001-0-2001-095
    - Beakes, Jennifer (Box 40, Item 2001-059)
    - Bob, Sarah (Box 40, Item 2001-060)
    - Bugallo, Helena (Box 40, Item 2001-061)
    - Elizabeth Currie (Box 40, Item 2001-062)
    - Infanti, Andrew (Box 40, Item 2001-063)
    - Klopotic, Julianne (Box 40, Item 2001-064)
    - MacDonald, Peyton (Box 40, Item 2001-065)
    - Mirelman, Sam (Box 40, Item 2001-066)
    - O'Donnell, Heather (Box 40, Item 2001-067)
    - Reinhardt, Haleigh (Box 40, Item 2001-068)
    - Rosenkranz, Thomas (Box 40, Item 2001-069)
    - Silverman, Adam (Box 40, Item 2001-070)
    - Smith, Steven Lyle (Box 40, Item 2001-071)
    - Zamboni, Maricio Gomes (Box 40, Item 2001-072)
    - 3rd Angle Ensemble (Box 40, Item 2001-073)
    - Albany Symphony Orchestra (Box 40, Item 2001-074)
    - American Baroque (Box 40, Item 2001-075)
    - Astral Artistic Services (Box 40, Item 2001-076)
    - Auros Group for New Music (Box 40, Item 2001-077)
    - Catskill Conservatory (Box 41, Item 2001-078)
    - Colorado Music Festival (Box 41, Item 2001-079)
    - Core Ensemble (Box 41, Item 2001-080)
    - CUBE Contemporary Chamber Ensemble (Box 41, Item 2001-081)
    - Das Neue Ensemble (Box 41, Item 2001-082)
    - Earplay (Musical group) (Box 41, Item 2001-083)
    - Empyrean Ensemble (Box 41, Item 2001-084)
    - London Sinfonietta (Box 41, Item 2001-085)
    - New Music Works (Box 41, Item 2001-086)
    - New Music Works (Box 41, Item 2001-087)
    - North/South Consonance (Musical group) (Box 41, Item 2001-088)
    - North/South Consonance (Musical group) (Box 41, Item 2001-089)
    - Orchestra 2001 (Box 41, Item 2001-090)
    - Pekarsky Percussion Ensemble (Box 41, Item 2001-091)
    - Savannah Symphony Orchestra (Box 41, Item 2001-092)
    - Voices of Change (Box 41, Item 2001-093)
    - The Walden School (Box 41, Item 2001-094)
    - Zeitgeist (Musical group) (Box 41, Item 2001-095)
  - Scores, 2001, F.; Item 2001-096-2001-098
    - Zamboni, Mauricio F H Crazy, undated, 1 score (16 p.); 22 x 33 cm. (Box 80, Item 2001-096)
      For narrator, violin, and percussion.
    - Zamboni, Mauricio Five Orchestral Moments, 1998-1999, 1 score (26 p.); 33 cm. (Box 80, Item 2001-097)
      For orchestra.
    - Zamboni, Mauricio Periclitancia, undated, 1 score (6 p.); 30 cm. (Box 80, Item 2001-098)
      For two marimbas.
- 2002, VIII.; Item 2002-001-2002-133
  - Individual award recipients, 2002, A.; Item 2002-001-2002-004
    - Cassidy, Aaron (Box 42, Item 2002-000)
    - Choi, Winston (Box 42, Item 2002-001)
    - Esler, Robert (Box 42, Item 2002-002)
    - Myers, Jeff (Box 42, Item 2002-003)
    - Valdes, Cristina (Box 42, Item 2002-004)
  - Organization award recipients, 2002, B.; Item 2002-005-2002-007
    - Alarm Will Sound (Musical group) (Box 42, Item 2002-005)
    - Alliance for the Arts (Box 42, Item 2002-005a)
    - Alliance for the Arts (Box 42, Item 2002-005b)
    - Concerts M (Box 42, Item 2002-005c)
    - Merkin Concert Hall (Meridian Ensemble) (Box 42, Item 2002-006)
    - Miller Theatre, Columbia University (Box 42, Item 2002-007)
    - Seattle Chamber Players (Box 42, Item 2002-007a)
    - Warebrook Contemporary Music Festival (Box 42, Item 2002-007b)
  - Individual applications, 2002, C.; Item 2002-08-2002-039
    - Bahr, Jason (Box 42, Item 2002-008)
    - Bechtold, Lynn (Box 42, Item 2002-009)
    - Bisesi, Jonathan (Box 42, Item 2002-010)
    - Carrasco, Laura (Box 42, Item 2002-011)
    - Carrasco, Ludwig (Box 43, Item 2002-012)
    - Choi, Denise (Box 43, Item 2002-013)
    - Coleman, Dan (Box 43, Item 2002-014)
    - Dillon, Candice (Box 43, Item 2002-015)
    - Eckman, Sarah (Box 43, Item 2002-016)
    - Feeney, Timothy (Box 43, Item 2002-017)
    - Frank, Gabriela Lena (Box 43, Item 2002-018)
    - Gee, Erin (Box 43, Item 2002-019)
    - Grossman, Jorge (Box 43, Item 2002-020)
    - Hallman, Joseph (Box 43, Item 2002-021)
    - Hanna, Trent (Box 43, Item 2002-022)
    - Hill, Adam (Box 43, Item 2002-023)
    - Kim, Suk-Jun (Box 43, Item 2002-024)
    - Lan, Mei-me (Box 43, Item 2002-025)
    - Lee, Wendy (Box 43, Item 2002-026)
    - Lin, Mei-Fang (Box 43, Item 2002-027)
    - Mastrian, Stacy Lynn (Box 43, Item 2002-028)
    - Melland, Justin Joseph (Box 43, Item 2002-029)
    - Montanaro, Larisa (Box 43, Item 2002-030)
    - Notareschi, Loretta (Box 43, Item 2002-031)
    - Ruo, Huang (Box 43, Item 2002-032)
    - Rutherford, John (Box 43, Item 2002-033)
    - Saoud, Erick (Box 43, Item 2002-034)
    - Saulle, Joshua (Box 43, Item 2002-035)
    - Tignor, Scott (Box 43, Item 2002-036)